let questions = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "What is the capital of Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"01) Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte",
        options:[
            "01) Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte",
            "02) Anuradhapura",
            "03) Galle",
            "04) Kandy"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2,
        question: "What is the district where the mountain Piduruthalagala situated?",
        answer:"03) Nuwara-Eliya",
        options:[
            "01) Kegalle",
            "02) Badulla",
            "03) Nuwara-Eliya",
            "04) Kandy"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question: "For how many provinces is SriLanka divided?",
        answer:"03) 9 provinces",
        options:[
            "01) 5 provinces",
            "02) 15 provinces",
            "03) 9 provinces",
            "04) 21 provinces"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question: "In which continent Sri Lanka is located?",
        answer:"01) Asia",
        options:[
            "01) Asia",
            "02) Europe",
            "03) Australia",
            "04) Africa"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 5,
        question: "What are the official languages in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"04) Sinhala, Tamil and English",
        options:[
            "01) Sinhala and Tamil only",
            "02) Sinhala, Tamil and Hindi",
            "03) Sinhala and Chinese",
            "04) Sinhala, Tamil and English"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 6,
        question: "For what Rathnapura district famous for?",
        answer:"03) Gems",
        options:[
            "01) Rubber",
            "02) Cinnamon",
            "03) Gems",
            "04) Tea"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 7,
        question: "What is the longest river in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"04) River-Mahaweli",
        options:[
            "01) River-Kalani",
            "02) River-Manik",
            "03) River-Kalu",
            "04) River-Mahaweli"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 8,
        question: "What is the highest waterfall in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"02) Bambarakanda waterfall",
        options:[
            "01) Lakshapana waterfall",
            "02) Bambarakanda waterfall",
            "03) Makeli waterfall",
            "04) Bopath waterfall"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 9,
        question: "What is the most attractive railway route in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"03) Colombo - Badulla",
        options:[
            "01) Colombo - Matara",
            "02) Colombo - Trincomalee",
            "03) Colombo - Badulla",
            "04) Colombo - Jaffna"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 10,
        question: "What is the largest district in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"02) Anuradhapura",
        options:[
            "01) Kaluthara",
            "02) Anuradhapura",
            "03) Galle",
            "04) Monaragala"
        ]
    },
];